NYSUT Representative Assembly (RA) Audio-Visual materials 6174/013 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
NYSUT Representative Assembly (RA) Audio-Visual materials
1983- 2008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State United Teachers (NYSUT)
6174/013 AV
42.94 cubic feet
42.4 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
7164047
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 28, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 24, 2016
Biographical / Historical
New York State United Teachers (NYSUT) was created in 1972 by the merger of the New York State Teachers Association (NYSTA) and the United Teachers of New York (UTNY). NYSTA had been affiliated with the National Education Association (NEA), and UTNY with the American Federation of Teachers (AFT). UTNY was the statewide organization whose United Federation of Teachers (UFT), led by Albert Shanker, was the predominant teachers' union in New York City. In joining with United Teachers and affiliating with the AFT, NYSUT also became a member union of the AFL-CIO.
In 1976, NYSUT voted to disaffiliate with the NEA. Some locals left NYSUT and created the NYEA (New York Educators Association), which became the state affiliate for the NEA. In the early 1980s, NYEA changed its name to NEA-NY.
NYEA/NEA- NY viewed association with the AFL-CIO's industrial unions as undermining the professional image and independence of teachers. The two organizations also differed strongly on aspects of the governance structure, particularly with respect to ethnic minority representation, with NYSUT opposed to mandatory minimums. The rivalry between NYSUT and NYEA/NEA-NY in organizing new locals expended a great deal of resources for both labor organizations.
While competition with NYEA/NEA-NY was a constant focus of NYSUT's organizing efforts for teachers, NYSUT was also organizing college faculty members, nurses, and other non-teaching personnel. Once members were organized, NYSUT continued to advocate for teachers' and other workers' rights through contract support and legal services at the local level and political involvement at the state and federal levels, supporting candidates and legislation that protected funding, due process, and working conditions.
NEA-N Y merged with NYSUT in 2006, by which time NYSUT had grown to more than half a million members, becoming the largest union in New York State.
Scope and Contents
Speeches at Representative Assembly and other events featuring President Bill Clinton, U.S. Senator Hillary Clinton, U.S. Sen. Charles Schumer, Andrew Cuomo, and other elected officials; NYSUT presidents Richard Ianuzzi and Tom Hobart; vice presidents Maria Neira and Antonia Cortese; Al Shanker, Randi Weingarten, Sandra Feldman, and other officers, 1985-2006
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6174/017 MB: NYSUT General Officers Memorabilia 6174: NYSUT Records 6174 AV: NYSUT Audio-Visual Materials 6174 MB: NYSUT Memorabilia 6174 OH: NYSUT Oral History Interviews 6174 P: NYSUT Photographs 6174 PUBS: NYSUT Publications 6174/001: NYSUT President's Office Files 6174/001 P: NYSUT President's Office Photographs 6174/002: NYSUT Vice President's Office files 6174/003: NYSUT Division of Research and Educational Services. Files 6174/004: NYSUT Field Services Department Files 6174/004 AV: NYSUT Field Services Department Audio-Visual Material 6174/005: NYSUT Legislative Department Files 6174/006: NYSUT Public Relations Department Files 6174/007: NYSUT New York Special Task Force on Equity and Excellence in Education Files 6174/008: NYSUT Federation of Nurses and Health Professionals Files 6174/009: NYSUT Teacher Education Conference Board Files 6174/010: NYSUT Convention files 6174/011: NYSUT Mid-Hudson Regional Office Files 6174/012: NYSUT "Teachers United: The Rise of NYSUT" Research Notes 6174/014: NYSUT Alan Lubin Files 6174/015: NYSUT Boards of Directors Meetings 6174/016: NYSUT Vice-President's Office Maria Neira. Files 6174/017: NYSUT General Officers Records 6174/017 AV: NYSUT General Officers Audio-Visual Materials 6174/017 P: NYSUT General Officers Photographs 6174/018: NYSUT Division of Research and Educational Services, Maria Neira Files 6174/019: NYSUT Biography File
Teachers' unions -- New York (State); New York State United Teachers; New York State United Teachers, Representative Assembly
7164047
- Al Shanker, 1987 RA, 1 (Box 4)
  Scope and Contents
  parts 1-4, NYSUT -- AS-3
- Al Shanker, 1988 RA, 2 (Box 4)
  NYSUT -- AS-4 -- Edit Master
- Al Shanker, 1989 RA, 3 (Box 4)
  parts 1-2 -- NYSUT -- AS-5 -- Edit Master
- Al Shanker: Speech at Statewide In-Service Conference, 1989; 4 (Box 4)
  part 1-2 -- 12/4/1989 -- NYSUT -- AS-6
- Al Shanker: 1990 RA, 5 (Box 4)
  Edit master -- NYSUT -- AS-7
- Al Shanker: 1992 RA, 6 (Box 4)
  NYSUT -- AS-8 -- Edit Master
- New York State United Teachers: Opening General Session, March 3, 1994 - Grand Ballroom, New York Hilton & Towers, 7 (Box 4)
- Candids, 8 (Box 4)
- New York State United Teachers: Opening Session, March 3, 1994, 9 (Box 4)
- New York State United Teachers: Opening Session, General Session, March 4, 1994 (tape 2), 10 (Box 4)
- New York State United Teachers: Opening Session, General Session, March 4, 1994 (tape 1), 11 (Box 4)
- New York State United Teachers: Opening Session, Opening Session, March 3, 1994, 12 (Box 4)
- New York State United Teachers: Opening Session, General Session, March 4, 1994 (tape 1), 13 (Box 4)
- New York State United Teachers: Opening Session, General Session, March 4, 1994 (tape 2), 14 (Box 4)
- New York State United Teachers: Opening Session, General Session, March 4, 1994 (tape 2), 15 (Box 4)
- NYSUT: Tape 1, Friday AM, 1 (Box 5)
- NYSUT: Tape 2, Friday AM, 2 (Box 5)
- NYSUT: Tape 1, Friday PM, 3 (Box 5)
- NYSUT: Tape 1, Saturday AM, 4 (Box 5)
- NYSUT: Tape 1, Saturday PM, 5 (Box 5)
- NYSUT: Tape 2, Friday PM, 6 (Box 5)
- NYSUT: Tape 2, Saturday PM, 7 (Box 5)
- NYSUT: Tape 3, Saturday AM, 8 (Box 5)
- NYSUT: Tape tape 3, Saturday PM, 9 (Box 5)
- NYSUT: Tape 3, Friday PM, 10 (Box 5)
- NYSUT: Tape 4, Saturday AM, 11 (Box 5)
- NYSUT: Tape 4, Saturday PM, 12 (Box 5)
- Al D'Amato, On Education :30 Spot 10/28/1997, 13 (Box 5)
- NYSUT: Capital Steps, tape #5 -- 5/2/1997, 14 (Box 5)
- NYSUT - 1992 Rep. Assembly, 15 (Box 5)
- NYSUT - 1992 Rep. Assembly, 16 (Box 5)
  Friday 3/2 -- Window Dub
- NYSUT 1992 - Rep. Assembly, 17 (Box 5)
  Fri. 3/20
- NYSUT 1992 Rep. Seminar, 18 (Box 5)
  Saturday PM, March 21 -- Window Dub
- NYSUT 1992 Rep. Assembly, 19 (Box 5)
  Saturday PM - March 21 -- Window Dub
- NYSUT 1992 Rep. Assembly, 20 (Box 5)
  Thurs. 3/19 -- Window Dub
- NYSUT 1992 Rep. Assembly, 21 (Box 5)
  Sat. AM 3/21 -- Window Dub
- NYSUT 1992 Rep. Assembly, 22 (Box 5)
  Sat. AM 3/21
- Meeting the Challenges RA'96, 1996; 23 (Box 5)
  NYSUT tape 6 -- February 29-March 2, 1996 - New York City
- Meeting the Challenges RA'96, 1996; 24 (Box 5)
  NYSUT - Tape 5 -- February 29-March 2, 1996 - New York City
- Meeting the Challenges RA'96, 1996; 25 (Box 5)
  NYSUT - Tape 4 -- February 29-March 2, 1996 - New York City
- Meeting the Challenges RA'96, 1996; 26 (Box 5)
  NYSUT - Tape 3 - February 29-March 2, 1996 - New York City
- Meeting the Challenges RA'96, 1996; 27 (Box 5)
  NYSUT - Tape 2 - February 29-March 2, 1996 - New York City
- NYSUT 1996 RA Highlights, 28 (Box 5)
- Robert B. Reich: U.S. Secretary of Labor, 29 (Box 5)
- 1997 RA Highlights, 30 (Box 5)
- Al Shanker - Watertown Conference Part I - NYSUT, 31 (Box 5)
  AS-10
- Al Shanker - NYSUT - 1996 RA, 32 (Box 5)
  AS-11
- Al Shanker - 1995 RA - Part I, Part 2 - NYSUT, 33 (Box 5)
  AS-9
- 1997 RA Highlights, 1998; 34 (Box 5)
  from VHS - 4/28/1998
- Al D'Amato on Education, 1998; 1 (Box 6)
  4/28/1998
- NAFTA eye-witness - 4/23/1998, 2 (Box 6)
  Show Master
- Nat'l. Certification - 1998, 3 (Box 6)
- Toni Cortese introduction video - 1998, 4 (Box 6)
- Tom Hobart Introduction video -- 1998, 5 (Box 6)
- Vote COPE Scroll -- 1998, 6 (Box 6)
- Scroll Master -- 1998, 7 (Box 6)
- NYSUT Master - Since Last We Met, 8 (Box 6)
- Teacher SRP -- 1998, 9 (Box 6)
- NYSUT 1998 - tape 1, 10 (Box 6)
- NYSUT 1998 - tape 2, 11 (Box 6)
- NYSUT 1998 Speeches - Walter Dunn, 12 (Box 6)
- SRP of the Year, 13 (Box 6)
- Session 2 - Fri. PM -- 1998, 14 (Box 6)
- Session 1 - Fri. AM - 1998, 15 (Box 6)
- NYSUT 1998 Speeches - Tom Hobart, Randi Weingarten, Alan Lubin, Fred Nauman, Ed McElroy, Antonia Cortese, 16 (Box 6)
- Schumer 3/1999 --, 17 (Box 6)
  VHS Dub
- NYSUT - Niagara Falls - April 22, 1999, 18 (Box 6)
- NYSUT - April 23, 1999 - Morning Session, 19 (Box 6)
- NYS United Teachers 'Vision', 20 (Box 6)
- Richard Mills, 21 (Box 6)
- NAFTA Eye Witness - 4/23/1998, 22 (Box 6)
- Schumer, Kozol, Teacher of the Year -- 1998 NYSUT RA, 23 (Box 6)
- 1999 RA Highlights - version 1 - 6/21/1999, 24 (Box 6)
- News Clips - Alan Lubin, 25 (Box 6)
- Tenure: Setting the Record Straight, 26 (Box 6)
- 1998 NYSUT Deceased Delegates, 27 (Box 6)
- NYSUT - April 24, 1999 - Morning Session, 28 (Box 6)
- NYSUT - Apr 23 Afternoon Tape 2, 29 (Box 6)
- NYSUT - Sat Apr 24 -- Afternoon, 30 (Box 6)
- ABC-TV 20/20 -- 6/28/1999 -- Saipan Sweatshop, 31 (Box 6)
- NYSUT -- Apr 23 - Afternoon Tape 1, 32 (Box 6)
- 1998 RA Highlights, 33 (Box 6)
- NYSUT - April 24, 1999 -- Mid Morning Session, 34 (Box 6)
- 2001 RA -- 5/4/2001 -- tape 4, 1 (Box 7)
- 2001 RA -- 5/3/2001 -- tape 1, 2 (Box 7)
- 2001 RA -- 5/5/2001 -- tape 1, 3 (Box 7)
- 2001 RA -- 5/5/2001 -- tape 2, 4 (Box 7)
- 2001 RA -- 5/4/2001 -- tape 3, 5 (Box 7)
- 2001 RA -- 5/4/2001 -- tape 1, 6 (Box 7)
- NYSUT RA -- NYSUT Second Vice President, Walter Dunn, 7 (Box 7)
- #1 - 4/6/2000 -- Evening Session - President's Office File, 8 (Box 7)
- NYSUT RA -- NYSUT Teacher of the Year - Marilyn Lance, 9 (Box 7)
- Tape #8 - Day 3 -- 4/8/2000 - Last General Session, 10 (Box 7)
- Tape #3 - Day 2 - 4/7/2000, 11 (Box 7)
- NYSUT RA - Chorus of William Alexander School, 12 (Box 7)
- NYSUT RA - NYSUT Executive Vice President, Alan Lubin, 13 (Box 7)
- NYSUT RA - US Senator, Charles Schumer, 14 (Box 7)
- NYSUT RA - NYSUT Executive Vice President, Alan Lubin, 15 (Box 7)
- 1999 SRP Employee of the Year - LouAnn Coleman - 3/15/2000, 16 (Box 7)
- Tape #2 - 4/6/2000 - Day #1, 17 (Box 7)
- Tape 8, Day 3 - 4/08/2000 - Last General S, 18 (Box 7)
- NYSUT RA - The Young People's Chorus of New York City, 19 (Box 7)
- #1 - 4/06/2000 -- Evening Session Day #1, 20 (Box 7)
- NYSUT RA - NYSUT Teacher of the Year - Marilyn Lance, 21 (Box 7)
- Tape #6 - Day 3 - 4/8/2000 - NYSUT, 22 (Box 7)
- NYSUT RA - New York City Labor Chorus, 23 (Box 7)
- Tape #5 - Day 3 -- 4/8/2000, 24 (Box 7)
- Tape #7 - Day 3 - 4/8/2000 - NYSUT, 25 (Box 7)
- NYSUT RA -- NYSUT First Vice President, Toni Cortese, 26 (Box 7)
- NYSUT RA - NYSUT President Tom Hobart, 27 (Box 7)
- Tape #5 - Day 3 - 4/8/2000 - NYSUT, 28 (Box 7)
- Tape #2 - Day #1 - 4/6/2000 - NYSUT, 29 (Box 7)
- NYS Labor-Religion Coalition Delegation/Sweatfree, 30 (Box 7)
- Giuliani Speaks - 3/15/2000, 31 (Box 7)
- Tape #7 - 4/8/2000 - Day 3 - NYSUT, 32 (Box 7)
- 2001 RA - 5/5/2001 - tape #3, 33 (Box 7)
- 2001 RA -- 5/3/2001 -- tape #2, 34 (Box 7)
- 2001 RA -- 5/4/2001 -- tape #2, 35 (Box 7)
- NYSUT RA - NYSUT SRP of the Year - Lou Anne Coleman, 36 (Box 7)
- Tape #4 - Day 2 - 4/7/2000 - NYSUT, 37 (Box 7)
- NYSUT RA - US Senator, Charles Schumer, 38 (Box 7)
- NYSUT 2002: NYSUT Polling Center, 1 (Box 8)
- NYSUT 2002: 9:11 Video Module, 2 (Box 8)
- NYSUT 2002: Teacher of the Year, GCG, 3 (Box 8)
- Political Action, 4 (Box 8)
- NYSUT, 5 (Box 8)
- NYSUT 2002: SRPs Video Module, 6 (Box 8)
- SOTA Singers, 7 (Box 8)
- SRP-2001, 8 (Box 8)
- UFT IB Rally 2002, 9 (Box 8)
- UFT Rally IA - 2002, 10 (Box 8)
- UFT Rally 2A - 2002, 11 (Box 8)
- UFT Rally 2B - 2002, 12 (Box 8)
- UFT Rally 3A - 2002, 13 (Box 8)
- UFT 3AQ Rally - 2002, 13 (Box 8)
- Bill Clinton - 2001 RA, 15 (Box 8)
- GCG NYSUT 2002 - Saturday Afternoon 4/27/2002 - tape #9, 16 (Box 8)
- GCG - NYSUT 2002 - Saturday morning - 4/27/2002 - Tape #7, 17 (Box 8)
- GCG - NYSUT 2002 - Saturday Morning - 4/27/2002 - Tape #8, 18 (Box 8)
- GCG - NYSUT 2002 - Friday Afternoon - 4/26/2002 - Tape #6, 19 (Box 8)
- NYSUT, 20 (Box 8)
- Ron Clark: American Disney Teacher of the Year - 2001 RA, 21 (Box 8)
- COLA, 22 (Box 8)
- Standard Assessments - 2001 RA, 23 (Box 8)
- Political Action - 2001 RA, 24 (Box 8)
- Speaker Sheldon Siler - 2001 RA, 25 (Box 8)
- Thomas Y. Hobart, Jr. - 2001 RA, 26 (Box 8)
- Joseph Solomon: Freedom's Poem - 2001 RA, 27 (Box 8)
- Senator Hillary Clinton - 2001 RA, 28 (Box 8)
- Sandra Feldman - 2001 RA, 29 (Box 8)
- Disney Learning Partnership - American Teacher Awards - NY Teacher Conference Segment - Final Cut TRT, 30 (Box 8)
- Only a Teacher - March 13, 2001, 31 (Box 8)
- Barbara Bartoletti, 1 (Box 9)
- Constituent Award Winners, 2 (Box 9)
- Constituent Award Winners, 3 (Box 9)
- A Women's Place is in Her Union, 4 (Box 9)
- Sandra Feldman - 2002 RA, 5 (Box 9)
- Sheldon Silver - 2002 RA, 6 (Box 9)
- 9-11 Heroes, 7 (Box 9)
- Teacher of the Year NYSUT - 2002 RA, 8 (Box 9)
- SRP of the Year - NYSUT - 2002 RA, 9 (Box 9)
- Ivan Tiger - 2002 RA, 10 (Box 9)
- Hobart, Lubin, Tiger, Cortese, Dunn - 2003 RA, April 3-5, 11 (Box 9)
- Aids in Africia - 2002 RA, 12 (Box 9)
- Hobart, Lubin, Tiger, C, Dunn - 2003 RA, April 3-5, 13 (Box 9)
- Clinton, Dean, Kerry, 14 (Box 9)
- Hobart, Lubin, Tiger, Cortese, Dunn - 2003 RA, April 3-5, 15 (Box 9)
- Shriver - 2003 RA, April 3-5, 16 (Box 9)
- Bill Mulrow - 2002 RA, 17 (Box 9)
- Denis Hughes - 2002 RA, 18 (Box 9)
- Richard Mills - 2002 RA, 19 (Box 9)
- Alan Hevesi - 2002 RA, 20 (Box 9)
- Lynn Costello Recognition - 2002 RA, 21 (Box 9)
- Concert Choir of Bayside HS (Queens) - 2002 RA, 22 (Box 9)
- Choral Ensemble of Brooklyn Tech. HS - 2002 RA, 23 (Box 9)
- Andrew Cuomo, 24 (Box 9)
- Alan Lubin - 2002 RA, 25 (Box 9)
- Randi Weingarten - 2002 RA, 26 (Box 9)
- Carl McCall - 2002 RA, 27 (Box 9)
- John Faso - 2002 RA, 28 (Box 9)
- GCG - NYSUT 2002 - Friday Morning 4/26/2002 - tape #2, 29 (Box 9)
- GCG - NYSUT 2002 - Thursday Night 4/25/2002 - tape #1, 30 (Box 9)
- GCG - NYSUT 2002 - Friday Afternoon 4/26/2002 - tape #4, 31 (Box 9)
- GCG - NYSUT 2002 - Friday Morning 4/26/2002 - tape #3, 32 (Box 9)
- GCG - NYSUT 2002 - Saturday Afternoon 4/27/2002 - tape #10, 33 (Box 9)
- GCG - NYSUT 2002 - Friday Afternoon 4/26/2002 - tape #5, 34 (Box 9)
- 2006 NYSUT RA - Constituent Awards, 1 (Box 10)
  Dub
- NYSUT - 2002 RA, 2 (Box 10)
- NYSUT - Vote COPE -, 1996; 3 (Box 10)
  Rev. 2/27/1996 -- MASTER
- 2006 Awards, 4 (Box 10)
- NYSUT 1996 Issues -- 1-New Generation; 2-Improving The Climate for Public Education; 3-NYSUT: Meeting the Challenges, 5 (Box 10)
- A History of NYSUT - Pres. Office File copy, 6 (Box 10)
- A Proud Tradition, 7 (Box 10)
- Feldman - 2003 RA, April 3-5, 8 (Box 10)
- Hobart, Lubin, Tiger, Cortese, Dunn -- 2003 RA, April 3-5, 9 (Box 10)
- Hobart, Lubin, Tiger, Cortese, Dunn - 2003 RA, April 3-5, 10 (Box 10)
- NYSUT building Bridges - 5/2/2006, 11 (Box 10)
- NYSUT - 5/5/2006, 12 (Box 10)
- NYSUT - 5/5/2006, 13 (Box 10)
- NYSUT - 5/5/2006, 14 (Box 10)
- NYSUT - 5/5/2006, 15 (Box 10)
- NYSUT - 5/5/2006, 16 (Box 10)
- NYSUT - 5/5/2006, 17 (Box 10)
- Tom Hobart, The Quiet Achiever, 18 (Box 10)
- C&C Visual - AFT & NYSUT: the Rebirth of Democracy - 7/27/2005, 19 (Box 10)
- Bagpiper - 2003 RA, April 3-5, 20 (Box 10)
- New York State United Teachers, 21 (Box 10)
- Bagpiper - 2003 RA, April 3-5, 22 (Box 10)
- Since We Last Met - 2003 RA, April 3-5, 23 (Box 10)
- Mills - 2003 RA, April 3-5, 24 (Box 10)
- Charles Schumer's address to NYSUT at 1998 RA and 1999 RA (Box 12)
- Giuliani Speaks NYSUT RA, 2000 (Box 13)
- NYSUT 201 RA 5/3/01 #1 (Box 14)
- NYSUT 2001 RA 5/3/01 #2 (Box 15)
- NYSUT 2001 RA 5/4/01 #1 (Box 16)
- NYSUT 2001 RA 5/4/01 #2 (Box 17)
- NYSUT 2001 RA 5/4/01 #3 (Box 18)
- NYSUT 2001 RA 5/4/01 #4 (Box 19)
- NYSUT 2001 RA 5/5/01 #1 (Box 20)
- NYSUT 2001 RA 5/5/01 #2 (Box 21)
- NYSUT 2001 RA 5/5/01 #3 (Box 22)
- NYSUT 2002 Hilton New York, Thursday Night 4/25/02 Tape #1 (Box 23)
- NYSUT 2002 Hilton New York, Friday Morning, 4/26/02, Tape #2 (1 of 2) (Box 24)
- NYSUT 2002 Hilton New York, Friday Morning, 4/26/02, Tape #3 (2 of 2) (Box 25)
- NYSUT 2002 Hilton New York, Friday Afternoon, 4/26/02, Tape #4 (1 of 3) (Box 26)
- NYSUT 2002 Hilton New York, Friday Afternoon, 4/26/02, Tape #5 (2 of 3) (Box 27)
- NYSUT 2002 Hilton New York, Friday Afternoon, 4/26/02, Tape #6 (3 of 3) (Box 28)
- NYSUT 2002 Hilton New York, Saturday Morning, 4/27/02, Tape #1 (1 of 2) (Box 29)
- NYSUT 2002 Hilton New York, Saturday Morning, 4/27/02, Tape #8 (2 of 2) (Box 30)
- NYSUT 2002 Hilton New York, Saturday Afternoon, 4/27/02, Tape #9 (1 of 2) (Box 31)
- NYSUT 2002 Hilton New York, Saturday Afternoon, 4/27/02, Tape #10 (2 of 2) (Box 32)
- May 3, 2003, March for Public Education, Albany, New York (Box 33)
- NYSUT 2003 RA General Session #1 (Box 34)
- NYSUT 2003 RA General Session 2, Disk 1 (Box 35)
- NYSUT 2003 RA General Session 2, Disk 2 (Box 36)
- NYSUT 2003 RA General Session 3, Disk 1 (Box 37)
- NYSUT 2003 RA General Session 3, Disk 2 (Box 38)
- NYSUT 2003 RA General Session 3, Disk 3 (Box 39)
- NYSUT 2003 RA General Session 4, Disk 1 (Box 40)
- NYSUT 2003 RA General Session 4, Disk 2 (Box 41)
- NYSUT 2003 RA General Session 4, Disk 3 (Box 42)
- 2004 NYSUT RA, March 25-27, 2004, NYC Hilton / Albert Shanker Award to H. Carl McCall (Box 43)
- NYSUT President Tom Hobart's Farewell speech to Staff, November 1, 2004 -- (Box 44)
- 2004 NYSUT RA, March 25-27, 2004, NYC Hilton (Box 45)
- 2004 NYSUT RA, March 2527, 2004, NYC Hilton (Box 46)
- 2004 NYSUT RA, March 25-27, 2004, NYC Hilton (Box 47)
- New York State United Teachers, RA 2004, Alan Lubin (Box 48)
- 2004 NYSUT RA, March 25-27, 2004, NYC Hilton / Secretary-Treasurer Ivan Tiger Speech (Box 49)
- 2004 NYSUT RA, March 25-27, 2004, NYC Hilton / Political Speeches (Box 50)
- Hilton / President Tom Hobart, State of the Union (Box 51)
- 2004 NYSUT RA, March 25-27, 2004, NYC Hilton / Second VP Walter Dunn Speech (Box 52)
- 2004 NYSUT RA, March 25-27, 2004, NYC Hilton (Box 53)
- NYSUT RA 2004 Disc 1 (Box 54)
- NYSUT RA 2004 Disc 2 (Box 55)
- NYSUT RA 2004 Disc 3 (Box 56)
- NYSUT RA 2004 Disc 4 (Box 57)
- Toni Cortese Tribute Dinner (Widescreen Format), 1/28/05, Saratoga Springs, NY, 2005 (Box 58)
- SONY Training Videos: Orientation, Protective Behaviors (Box 59)
- NYSUT RA 2005, Saturday 4/9/05 PM Session - Part 1 (Box 60)
- NYSUT RA 2005, Saturday 4/9/05 PM Session - Part 2 (Box 61)
- NYSUT RA 2005, All Tom Hobart Tributes (Box 62)
- NYSUT RA 2005, Thursday 4/7/05 PM Session (Box 63)
- Foot Artwork (Box 64)
- Murphy Putnam, Shorr & Partners, NYSUT Compilation. (Box 65)
- Setting the stage for your success -- NYSUT Jason McElwain (Box 66)
- CD#A Thursday Photo Options -- NYS United Teachers (NYSUT) (Box 67)
- Unification (Box 68)
- AFT Hurricane Relief Video, 1 (Box 69)
- AFT Hurricane Relief Video (Box 70)
- AFT & NYSUT - The Rebirth of Democracy -- 7/27/05, 2005 (Box 71)
- NYSUT 2005 RA, Tom Hobart Tribute Segment (Widescreen) 4/15/05 (Box 72)
- NYSUT 2005 RA, Speeches - Disc 1 of 2 4/15/05 (Box 73)
- NYSUT 2005 RA, Speeches - Disc 2 of 2 4/15/05 (Box 74)
- NYSUT RA 2005, Friday 4/8/05 AM Session (Box 75)
- NYSUT RA 2005, Friday 4/8/05 PM Session (Box 76)
- NYSUT RA 2005, Friday 4/8/05 PM Session Part 2 (Box 77)
- NYSUT RA 2005, Saturday 4/9/05 AM Session - Part 1 (Box 78)
- NYSUT RA 2005, Saturday 4/9/05 AM Session Part 2 (Box 79)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.5.2006 (Box 80)
- NYSUT RA 2006 5.5.2006 (Box 81)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.4.2006 (Box 82)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.4.2006 (Box 83)
- 2006 Political Speeches - Alan Hevesi, Hilary Rodham Clinton, David Patterson (Box 84)
- NYUT RA 2006 - 5.5.2006 (Box 85)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.5.2006 (Box 86)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.5.2006 (Box 87)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.5.2006 (Box 88)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.6.2006 (Box 89)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.6.2006 (Box 90)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.5.2006 (Box 91)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.5.2006 (Box 92)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.6.2006 (Box 93)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.6.2006 (Box 94)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.5.2006 (Box 95)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.5.2006 (Box 96)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.4.2006 (Box 97)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.5.2006 (Box 98)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.5.2006 (Box 99)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.6.2006 (Box 100)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.5.2006 (Box 101)
- NYSUT B Roll 2 -- May 4, 2006 (Box 102)
- NYSUT B Roll -- May 4-6, 2006 (Box 103)
- NYSUT B Roll 1 -- May 4-6, 2006 (Box 104)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - Final Prompter (Box 105)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - Final Prompter (Box 106)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.5.2006 (Box 107)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.5.2006 (Box 108)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.6.2006 (Box 109)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.6.2006 (Box 110)
- 2006 RA Unification of NYSUT & NEA/NY - May 4-6, 2006 (Box 111)
- 2006 RA Unification of NYSUT & NEA/NY - May 4-6, 2006 (Box 112)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.6.2006 (Box 113)
- NYSUT B Roll 2 - May 4-6, 2006 (Box 114)
- NYSUT B Roll 3 - May 4-6, 2006 (Box 115)
- NYSUT B Roll 3 - May 4-6, 2006 (Box 116)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.6.2006 (Box 117)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.6.2006 (Box 118)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.6.2006 (Box 119)
- 2006 RA Educational Issues - Urbanski/School Super/Mayor/School Board, Commissioner of Education, Toni Cortese (Box 120)
- 2006 Political Speeches - Alan Hevesi, Hillary Rodham Clinton, David Patterson (Box 121)
- 2006 Educational Issues - Urbanski/School Super/Mayor/School Board, Commissioner of Education, Toni Cortese (Box 122)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.5.2006 (Box 123)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.6.2006 (Box 124)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.6.2006 (Box 125)
- NYSUT B Roll 3 (Box 126)
- NYSUT B Roll 2 (Box 127)
- NYSUT RA 2006 - 5.4.2006 (Box 128)
- NYSUT B Roll 1 (Box 129)
- Social Justice Issues - Social Justice, Fair Trade (Box 130)
- Social Justice Issues - Social Justice, Fair Trade (Box 131)
- 2006 RA Officers' Speeches -- Richard Iannuzzi - State of the Union, Maria Neira, Ivan Tiger, Alan Lubin, Kathleen Donahue (Box 132)
- NYSUT RA May 4-6, 2006 - School Groups (Box 133)
- NYSUT RA May 4-6, 2006 - School Groups (Box 134)
- 2006 Constituency Award Winners - Retiree of the Year, SRP of the year, NYS Teacher of the Year, Healthcare Professional of the Year, Not for Ourselves, Higher Education (Box 135)
- 2006 RA Special Presentations: Brenda Mitchell, Sandy Feldman, Award Dessert Reception, J. Mack, Tom Hobart (Box 136)
- 2006 RA Special Presentation: Brenda Mitchell, Sandy Feldman, Award Dessert Reception, J.Mack, Tom Hobart (Box 137)
- 2006 RA Officers' Speeches: Richard Iannuzzi - State of the Union, Maria Neira, Ivan Tiger, Alan Lubin, Kathleen Donahue (Box 138)
- Officer Speeches, Alan B. Lubin, Ivan Tiger (Box 139)
- Officer Speeches: Richard C. Iannuzzi, Maria Neira (Box 140)
- Officer Speeches: Kathleen M. Donahue, Robin Rapaport (Box 141)
- Videos - We are NYSUT, Every Child Counts (Box 142)
- Teacher of the Year: Izzo Hi-Ed Members of the Year: Young & Schuler Mauk (Box 143)
- NYSUT 2005 RA - April 7-9, 2005, New York City (Box 144)
- Sandy Feldman Award Ceremony, Langiulli-Pietrantoni-Hegge (Box 145)
- 2007 Constituency Awards (Box 146)
- 2008 Constituency Awards -- 2 CDs in one case (Box 147)
- Bill Duffy: News Report on NYSUT - RA 1983, 1 (Box 148)
- RA 85 - Vote COPE Cutaways - Cump. Training Room, 2 (Box 148)
- RA 86, 3 (Box 148)
- RA 86, 4 (Box 148)
- RA 86, 5 (Box 148)
- Cuomo II, Ambach II, 6 (Box 148)
- RA 85 - Floor Motion, 7 (Box 148)
- RA 85 - Part 100, 8 (Box 148)
- RA 85 - Ambock 2, Chester Finn 1, 9 (Box 148)
- RA 85, 10 (Box 148)
- RA 85 - Golden Apple, Cuomo 1, 11 (Box 148)